Muhammad Kamran

Email Phone Number

mohammadkamran1515@gmail.com 0307-5587985, 0307-8907120

Objectives

I will be the loyal to company projects and will not steal any confidential of company. I will work in company to get good experience about professional skills and management. My behavior will always be polite and highly respectable towards other colleagues. Insha'Allah!

Personal Details

Full Name Muhammad Kamran

Father Name Muhammad Suleman

Date of Birth 08 July, 1997

Current Address House 10, Qureshi Plaza behind Khushhali bank

Jhelum, Punjab, Pakistan

Permanent Address Village Athar, Tehsil PD khan, District Jhelum

Contact & Work Samples

Portfolio: https://bit.ly/2XspDB7Portfolio: https://bit.ly/3tccKqK

Email: mohammadkamran1515@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://bit.ly/3pDofXF

Contact: 0307-5587985, 0307-8907120

Academic Qualification

Degree	Institute	Marks	Percentage	Duration
BS Information Technology	Government postgraduate college Jhelum (University of Gujrat)	3.36/4.00	74.9%	2016-2020
F.sc Pre- Engineering	Government postgraduate college Jhelum	665/1100	60.45%	2013-2015

Matriculation	Ali Public Higher	814/1050	77.52%	2011-2013
	Secondary School			
	Athar District Jhelum			
Google Digital	Google inc	passed		Oct 2020
Marketing	_			
Certificate				

Professional Skills

- Custom Web Development
 - Front End Web Development (HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap4, JavaScript)
 - Back End web development (PHP, MySQL, Laravel)
 - Responsive web development
- > CMS
 - WordPress and Shopify (Store Creation and management)
 - Theme Customization
 - Page Builders (Elementor)
 - Website Security and maintenance
- > SEO
 - Website Speed and Optimization
 - Keyword Optimizations and Ranking
 - Page Speed optimization
 - Off page SEO
- Other Skills
 - MS office
 - Excellent Communication Skills
 - Teaching

Professional Experience

- Worked as a Content Writer in Big Scoop Solutions Ltd (July 2017 - Aug 2017)
- Worked as a Computer Teacher in Computer City (July 2019 - March 2020)
- Worked as an Internee in a software company (XfinitySoft)
 (Oct 2020 January 2021)
- Worked on Freelancing Sites as Freelance Web Developer (Since 2019)
- Worked as Laravel Developer in a software company (Unique-Links)
 (January 27 2021 31 May 2021)

➤ Worked as an Ecommerce Trainer in Computer City (June 07, 2021 – August 08, 2021)

Languages & Hobbies

- Book Reading
- > Internet Surfing and Music Listening
- > Entertainment
- > English, Punjabi and Urdu Speaking